

LES BOGDAN

PHP DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

During my 15-years of working in developing my own website www.jubuti.com and other little projects related to web developing, i have acumulated a lot of experience in PHP and JavaScript developing, and CSS styling. I look forward to new challenges in developing various websites because they make me better and intrigue me.

CONTACT DETAILS

- +40-724-154-222
- bogdan19802010@gmail.com
- Romania, Timis, Giarmata-Vii Str. Infratirea, No. 140A
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/bogdan-les-892636155 https://github.com/BogdanLes

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jubuti.com

Owner and Developer | January 2008 - Present

- PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySql programmer for www.jubuti.com international business and professional database, which I own
- I am also in progress of developing an online shop for small and medium businesses

Gold for Gold

Sales Consultant | September 2021 - March 2023

Consultation/Evaluation/Sale of gold and diamond jewelry

■ Timisoara International Airport

Merceologist | October 2000 - September 2003

• Supply Office - purchase of goods and services for the institution

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

2023

The Informal School of IT

2024

course: Java Development

title: Junior software developer

project: Web interface for a business database

- Procedural programing: variables, operators, clauses, loops, arrays, methods
- OOP: Classes, Objects, Interfaces, Enams, Abstraction, Encapsulation, Inheritance, Polymorphism, Composition, Design patterns

- Collections: ArrayList, LinkedList, HashSet, TreeSet, HashMap, TreeMap, Exception handling, Threads, Lamda
- File handling, XML, SQL, PostgreSQL
- · Maven, Intellij IDEA, Git, Github

W3Schools 2023

course: PHP

title: PHP Developer

https://verify.w3schools.com/609023LF1

- Procedural programing: variables, operators, clauses, loops, arrays, functions, regular expressions, superglobals, exceptions, date, filters
- OOP: Classes, Objects, Interfaces, Abstraction, Encapsulation, Inheritance, Polymorphism, Traits, Iterables
- Forms, AJAX, JSON, Cookies, Sessions
- File handling, XML, SimpleXML, XML DOM, SQL, MySQL

2023 W3Schools

course: C++

title: C++ Developer

https://verify.w3schools.com/609023LF1

- Procedural programing: variables, operators, clauses, loops, arrays, functions, structures, enums, pointers
- OOP: Classes, Objects, Abstraction, Encapsulation, Inheritance, Polymorphism
- · File handling

2004 The West University of Timișoara

2006

Master's degree

Faculty of Economic Sciences

specialization: Strategic Management of Organizations

dissertation: Analysis of the strategies of Bancii Comerciale Romane S.A. in the period 2001-2004

- Management: principles, functions, styles
- · Methods and techniques for evaluating businesses and products based on the market and competition

2000 **Banat University**

2004

Bachelor's degree

Faculty of Economic Sciences

specialization: Finance-Accounting

title: Licensed Economist

bachelor's thesis: Study on the use of fixed funds at S.C. Sabico-Impex SRL

- · Accounting, Budget and taxation, Finance, Economic-financial analysis
- Marketing, Management, Statistics, Microeconomics, Macroeconomics, Capital markets



Grigore Moisil Informatics High School

Baccalaureate diploma

title: Junior software developer

• First contact with programing in Pascal and C++, and first interaction with a database FoxPro

SKILLS

- PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, MySQL, XML, AJAX, JSON, jQuery, Apache, NetBeans, GIT
- C, C++, JAVA, Maven, IntelliJ IDEA, PostgreSQL, CodeBlocks, Software Design Patterns, Object-Oriented Programming
- Analytical Skills, Teamwork, Adaptability, Problem solving, Critical thinking, Creativity and Innovation, Self-Motivation and Initiative

LANGUAGES

- Romanian (Native)
- English (Fluent)

HOBBIES

• Football, Strategy Games, Fishing, Fitness